In this segment we're going to be talking about another trick type of a brush and this one’s going to be behind the back brush.
Now to do the behind the back brush obviously it has to be somewhere around your waist.
And what you want to do is that's the basic brush but you're going to want to do it so your hand is behind your back.
Now obviously there's not a lot of room there when you're doing a behind the back brush but if you time it just right and get your body out of the way you should be able to do it.
We're going to do it with a clock spin first.
From here, brush.
Ryan's a little bit better at it so he's going to try a couple of brushes.
You can do it on either side.
There's the right handed brush.
Now he's going to try the left handed brush with a clock spin.
There it is.
There's the nesting.
So you can do it on either side you just have to be aware of which direction the Frisbee is spinning.
Try to make sure you get your body out of the way when you're brushing this way and this way.
That's a behind the back brush.